Saving the neighborhood one sole at a time.
The Cobbler is a fantasy, comedy, drama film directed by Tom McCarthy.
Max Simkin repairs shoes in the same New York shop that
has been in his family for generations.
Disenchanted with the grind of daily life, Max stumbles upon a magical heirloom that allows
him to step into the lives of his customers and see the world in a new way.
Sometimes walking in another man's shoes is the only way
one can discover who they really are.
Max Simkin, played by Adam Sandler.
Leon Ludlow, played by Method Man.
Abraham Simkin, played by Dustin Hoffman.
Jimmy, played by Steve Buscemi.
Carmen Herrara, played by Melonie Díaz.
Elaine Greenawalt, played by Ellen Barkin.
The Cobbler is a 2014 American magic realism comedy-drama film directed
by Tom McCarthy and cowritten by McCarthy with Paul Sado.
The film stars Adam Sandler as a cobbler who finds himself able to
assume to the form of anyone by putting on their shoes.
The supporting cast includes Cliff "Method Man" Smith, Ellen Barkin, Melonie Diaz, Dan
Stevens, Fritz Weaver, Yul Vazquez, Steve Buscemi and Dustin Hoffman.
The Cobbler premiered at the 2014 Toronto International Film Festival,
where it was screened in the Special Presentations section.
The film was released in U.S.
theaters on March 13, 2015, by Image Entertainment.
The Cobbler was panned by critics, and was a box-office bomb,
grossing $6.5 million on a $10 million budget.
The film explores themes of new york city, gang leader,
cobbler, jewish family, body switch.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.